(Q11（单选）) Good morning everyone. My name’s Joy Parkins and I’m the restaurant manager. 大家早上好，我叫Joy Parkins，是这家餐厅的经理。
And I understand that none of you’ve had any previous experience as kitchen assistants. 我知道大家之前都没有做过厨房助理的经验。
[11定位词（同义替换）enjoy = like， most 也原词重现] Well, you might be feeling a bit nervous now, but most of our kitchen assistants say they enjoy the work. 你们现在可能有点紧张，不过大多数厨房助理都表示很喜欢这份工作。
[✅A， different things to do = variety of work] OK, they might get shouted at sometimes, but it’s nothing personal, and they’re pleased that they have so many different things to do, which means they never get bored. 当然，有时候难免会被训几句，但那并不是针对个人。而且工作内容很多样，所以基本不会觉得无聊。
[❌C，偷换概念， might think 给机会晋升， 完全不是 员工 like 的点] And I’ll tell you straightaway that if you do well, we might think about moving you up and giving you some more responsibility. 我先告诉大家，如果表现出色，我们会考虑给你们晋升，并安排更多职责。
(Q12) Right, well, you’ve all shown up on time, which is an excellent start. 很好，大家今天都准时到了，这是一个相当不错的开始。
[❌C footwear =shoes，选项C出现， 但 否定原文， 大家都穿了合适的鞋 不等于 经理在concered] Now I’m glad to see none of you have unsuitable footwear, so that’s good - you need to be careful as the floors can get very wet and slippery. 我很高兴看到大家都穿了合适的鞋。不过还是要注意，厨房地面经常会又湿又滑。
[❌B 提到了hair， 扎好了 get it well 否定原文「担心」。   ✅A - rings&bracelets = jewellery， hazard = concern的含义] Those of you with long hair have got it well out of the way, but some of you’ll need to remove your rings and bracelets - just put them somewhere safe for today, and remember to leave them at home tomorrow, as they can be a safety hazard. 留长发的同事都已经把头发扎好了。不过有些人还需要把戒指和手镯摘下来，今天先放在安全的地方保管。明天记得直接放在家里，因为这些饰品可能带来安全隐患。
(Q13) [🟢 定位词 busy， ✅C don't have any table free = fully booked] Now it’s going to be a busy day for you all today - we don’t have any tables free for this evening, and only a few for lunch. 今天大家会比较忙，因为晚餐时段已经没有空桌了，午餐时段也只剩下少量座位。
[❌B， 否定原文，absent 不在场的，原文 be back 。 ❌A未提及] Fortunately we’ve got our Head Chef back - he was away on holiday all last week which meant the other chefs had extra work. 幸运的是，我们的主厨已经回来了。他上周一直在休假，所以其他厨师这段时间都承担了额外的工作。
(Q14) Now, I’ll tell you a bit more about the job in a minute but first, some general regulations. 接下来我会详细介绍一下工作内容，不过先来说几条基本规定。
[🟢 提到了age，定位词 18 or order 都是指年龄。 ❌A出现， 否定原文] For all of you, whatever your age, there’s some equipment you mustn’t use until you’ve been properly trained, like the waste disposal system for example, for health and safety reasons. 无论年龄大小，在接受正式培训之前，有些设备大家都不能使用。比如垃圾处理系统，主要是出于卫生和安全方面的考虑。
[原词 18 出现，但说的under 18] Then I think there are two of you here who are under 18 - that’s Emma and Jake, isn’t it? 我记得这里有两位还未满18岁，是Emma和Jake，对吗？
[✅C 同义替换 解释类： for under 18， xxx out of bounds = 18 or order allow] Right. so for you two, the meat slicer is out of bounds. 好的，那么你们两位不能使用切肉机。
[❌B， 否定原文] And of course none of you are allowed to use the electric mixer until you’ve been shown how it works. 当然，在学习并掌握电动搅拌机的操作方法之前，任何人都不得使用它。
(Q15&16 多选) [🟢stressful 定位词] Now you may have heard that this can be a stressful job, and I have to say that can be true. 你们可能听说过这份工作压力不小，我得承认，这种说法确实有一定道理。
(Q17（配对题）) Now let me tell you about some of the people you need to know. 接下来给大家介绍几位需要认识的同事。