(Q11（单选）) Hi everyone, welcome to the Snow Centre. My name's Annie. I hope you enjoyed the bus trip from the airport - we've certainly got plenty of snow today! 大家好，欢迎来到雪地中心。我叫Annie。希望大家从机场坐巴士过来的路上玩得愉快。今天这里的积雪可是相当充足呢！
Well, you've come to New Zealand's premier snow and ski centre, and we've a whole load of activities for you during your week here. 这里是新西兰首屈一指的冰雪运动中心，在接下来的一周里，我们为大家安排了丰富多彩的活动。
[原词定位词 cross-country skiing] Most visitors come here for the cross-country skiing, where you're on fairly flat ground for most of the time, rather than going down steep mountain sides. 大多数游客来这里都是为了体验越野滑雪。这项运动大部分时间都在较为平坦的地面上进行，而不是从陡峭的山坡上滑下来。
[✅A：leave these and go off your own = get away 解释] There are marked trails, but you can also leave these and go off on your own and that's an experience not to be missed. 这里设有标记清晰的滑雪路线，不过你也可以离开既定路线，自由探索，这种体验绝对不容错过。
[❌C， 偷换概念，按你自己速度来 不等于 slow speed。    ❌B，否定原文， you can enjoy ...] You can go at your own speed - it's great aerobic exercise if you really push yourself,     ｜  or if you prefer you can just glide gently along and enjoy the beautiful scenery. 你可以按照自己的节奏前进。如果认真挑战自己，这会是一项很棒的有氧运动；当然，你也可以悠闲地滑行，一边欣赏沿途美丽的风景。
(Q12) [题干定位词 dog-sled trip] This afternoon, you'll be going on a dog-sled trip. 今天下午，大家将体验狗拉雪橇之旅。
[下文them，代词指代 本句提过的dogs] You may have seen our dogs on TV recently racing in the winter sled festival. 最近你们可能在电视上见过我们的雪橇犬，它们参加了冬季雪橇节的比赛。
[✅B 解释： if you want, you can have ... team = anyone can。 ➕ ❗️ 代词指代！！them - 上文提到过的dogs] If you want, you can have your own team for the afternoon and learn how to drive them, following behind our leader on the trail. 如果愿意的话，下午你可以拥有属于自己的雪橇犬队，并学习如何驾驭它们，跟随我们的领队沿着路线前进。
[✅A/C 未提及] Or if you'd prefer, you can just sit back in the sled and enjoy the ride as a passenger. 当然，如果你更喜欢轻松一点，也可以坐在雪橇上当乘客，尽情享受旅程。
(Q13) [题干定位词 原词 team relay event] At the weekend, we have the team relay event, and you're all welcome to join in. 周末我们将举行团队接力赛，欢迎大家踊跃参加。
[❌C， teacher会参加，没说is led by teacher - 偷换概念] We have a local school coming along, and a lot of the teachers are taking part too. 届时当地的一所学校也会参加，而且许多老师也会亲自上场。
[✅A everyone = all， 近义词， 加语境 participation 是 main focus] Participation rather than winning is the main focus, and there's a medal for everyone who takes part. 这项活动重在参与而非竞争，而且每位参赛者都能获得一枚奖牌。
[❌B，提到4，但是是4圈 4 laps，] Participants are in teams of two to four, and each team must complete four laps of the course. 参赛队伍由2至4人组成，每支队伍都需要完成赛道四圈。
(Q14) [定位词 snow-shoe] For your final expedition, you'll head off to Mount Frenner wearing a pair of special snow shoes which allow you to walk on top of the snow. 在最后一项探险活动中，大家将前往Frenner山，并穿上特制雪鞋，让你能够直接在积雪表面行走。
[❌A、 mine出现了，但否定原文 - though + few] This is an area where miners once searched for gold, though there are very few traces of their work left now. 这里曾经是矿工淘金的地区，不过如今已经很难看到他们留下的痕迹了。
[❌B flowers出现，但没提unusual的事儿，偷换概念] When the snow melts in summer, the mountain slopes are carpeted in flowers and plants. 到了夏天，积雪融化后，漫山遍野都会铺满鲜花和各种植物。
[✅C， summit顶峰= top of a mountain 近义词] It's a long ascent（/əˈsent/ n 上坡路）, though not too steep, and walkers generally take a couple of days to get to the summit and return. 虽然上山的路程较长，但坡度并不算陡。通常徒步者往返山顶需要两天左右的时间。
(Q15) [题干定位词 spend the night = accommodation] You'll spend the night in our hut half-way up the mountain. 大家将在半山腰的小木屋里过夜。
[题干动词 include 出现] That's included in your package for the stay. 住宿费用已经包含在你们的活动套餐中了。
[✅A drinking water= water for drinking] It's got cooking facilities, firewood and water for drinking. 小木屋内配备了烹饪设施、柴火以及饮用水。
For washing, we recommend you use melted snow, though, to conserve supplies. 不过为了节约物资，我们建议大家洗漱时使用融化后的雪水。
[❌B关键词luggage出现，但要收费] We can take your luggage up on our snowmobile for you for just ten dollars a person. 我们可以用雪地摩托帮大家把行李运上山，每人只需10美元。
[❌仅有cooking facilities， meal得自己带] The hut has cooking facilities so you can make a hot meal in the evening and morning, but you need to take your own food. 木屋内有烹饪设备，方便大家早晚做热食，不过食物需要自行携带。
(Q16) The weather on Mount Frenner can be very stormy. Frenner山的天气有时会非常恶劣。
[stay in = wait ✅B] In that case, stay in the hut - generally the storms don't last long. 如果遇到暴风雪天气，请待在木屋里。一般来说，风暴持续时间不会太长。
[❌A， 未提及， 关于bus 只是说也不会运行而已。] Don't stress about getting back here to the centre in time to catch the airport bus - they'll probably not be running anyway. 也不用担心赶不上返回机场的巴士，因为那种天气下巴士多半也不会运行。
[❌C，否定， only use ... real emergency] We do have an emergency locator beacon in the hut but only use that if it's a real emergency, like if someone's ill or injured. 木屋里配备了紧急定位信标，但只有在真正的紧急情况下才能使用，比如有人生病或受伤时。
(Q17（配对）) Now, let me tell you something about the different ski trails you can follow during your stay here. 接下来，我给大家介绍一下入住期间可以体验的几条滑雪路线。