(Q11 单选题) We'll be arriving at Branley Castle in about five minutes, but before we get there I'll give you a little information about the castle and what our visit will include. 我们将在五分钟后到达布兰利城堡，但在我们到达之前，我会给你一些关于城堡的信息，以及我们的参观将包括什么。
So in fact there's been a castle on this site for over eleven hundred years. 所以事实上这个地方的城堡已经有一千一百多年的历史了。
The first building was a fort constructed in 914 AD for defence against Danish invaders by King Alfred the Great's daughter, who ruled England at the time. 最早的建筑是一座防御丹麦入侵者的堡垒，是在公元914年由当时统治英格兰的阿尔弗雷德大帝的女儿建造的。
In the following century, after the Normans conquered England, the land was given to a nobleman called Richard de Vere, and he built a castle there that stayed in the de Vere family for over four hundred years. 在接下来的一个世纪里，诺曼人征服了英格兰，这块土地被给了一个叫Richard de Vere的贵族，他在那里建造了一座城堡，在接下来的四百多年都属于de Vere家族。
However, when Queen Elizabeth I announced that she was going to visit the castle in 1576, it was beginning to look a bit run down, and it was decided that rather than repair the guest rooms, they'd make a new house for her out of wood next to the main hall. 然而在1576年，当女王伊丽莎白一世宣布她将参观这座城堡时，它开始显得有些破旧不堪，于是城堡的管理人决定，与其去修缮客房，还不如在大厅旁边用木头给她造一座新房子。
She stayed there for four nights and apparently it was very luxurious, but unfortunately it was destroyed a few years later by fire. 她在那里住了四个晚上，新房非常豪华，但不幸的是几年后被大火烧毁了。
(Q12) In the seventeenth century the castle belonged to the wealthy Fenys family, who enlarged it and made it more comfortable. 在十七世纪，城堡属于富有的Fenys家族，他们扩建了城堡，使其更加舒适。
However, by 1982 the Fenys family could no longer afford to maintain the castle, even though they received government support, and they put it on the market. 然而，到了1982年，尽管得到了政府的支持，Fenys家族再也负担不起城堡的维护费用，并决定将其放到市场上出售。
It was eventually taken over by a company who owned a number of amusement parks, but when we get there I think you'll see that they've managed to retain the original atmosphere of the castle. 它最终被一家经营着许多游乐园的公司接管了，但我觉得等到了那里，你们就会发现他们已经设法保留了城堡原来的氛围。
(Q13) When you go inside, you'll find that in the state rooms there are life-like moving wax models dressed in costumes of different periods in the past, which even carry on conversations together. 当你们走进去的时候，你会发现在客厅里有栩栩如生的移动的蜡像，它们穿着过去不同时期的服装，甚至还能进行对话。
As well as that, in every room there are booklets giving information about what the room was used for and the history of the objects and furniture it contains. 此外，每个房间都有小册子，用来介绍房间的用途以及房间内家具摆件的历史。
(Q14) The castle parks quite extensive. At one time sheep were kept there, and in the nineteenth century the owners had a little zoo with animals like rabbits and even a baby elephant. 城堡的公园相当开阔，以前那里还养过绵羊。在十九世纪时，城堡的主人还有个小动物园，里面养着兔子，甚至还有一头小象。
Nowadays the old zoo buildings are used for public displays of paintings and sculpture. 现在，旧的动物园被用来向公众展示绘画和雕塑。
The park also has some beautiful trees, though the oldest of all, which dated back 800 years, was sadly blown down in 1987. 公园里还有一些美丽的树木，只是那最老的八百岁的古树，在1987年不幸被吹倒。
Now, you're free to wander around on your own until 4:30, but then at the end of our visit we'll all meet together at the bottom of the Great Staircase. 现在，你们可以自由行动到四点半，但参观结束时，我们就在大楼梯的底部集合。
We'll then go on to the long gallery, where there's a wonderful collection of photographs showing the family who owned the castle a hundred years ago having tea and cakes in the conservatory -and we'll then take you to the same place where afternoon tea will be served to you. 我们接下来将去到长廊，那里有许多很棒的照片，它们展示了一百年前的城堡主人们在温室里喝茶、吃蛋糕的样子，然后我们将带你们去和照片里同样的地方，你们将在那里享用下午茶。
(Q16 地图题) Now if you can take a look at your plans you'll see Branley Castle has four towers, joined together by a high wall, with the river on two sides. 现在看看你们手里的平面图，你们会发现布兰利城堡有四座塔，由一道高墙连接在一起，两侧都有河流。
Don't miss seeing the Great Hall. That's near the river in the main tower, the biggest one, which was extended and redesigned in the eighteenth century. 千万别错过大堂。大堂位于最大的主塔的下的河边，它在十八世纪得到扩建，并且被重新设计。
If you want to get a good view of the whole castle, you can walk around the walls. 如果你们想好好看看整个城堡，可以绕着墙走。
The starting point's quite near the main entrance - walk straight down the path until you get to the south gate, and it's just there. 起点就在正门附近，沿着小路一直走到南门，城堡就在那里。
Don't go on to the north gate - there's no way up from there. 别再走到北门了，从那儿开始就没路了。
(Q17) There'll shortly be a show in which you can see archers displaying their skill with a bow and arrow. 不久将有一场表演，你们可以看到弓箭手展示他们的弓箭技巧。
The quickest way to get there is to take the first left after the main entrance and follow the path past the bridge, then you'll see it in front of you at the end. 去看表演最快的方法是在进入正门后的第一个路口左转，沿着小路一直走过桥，然后你们就会看到弓箭表演在路的尽头处。
(Q18) If you like animals there's also a display of hunting birds - falcons and eagles and so on. 如果你们喜欢动物，这里也有猎鸟表演——猎鹰和老鹰等等。
If you go from the main entrance in the direction of the south gate, but turn right before you get there instead of going through it, you'll see it on your right past the first tower. 你们可以在进入正门后朝南门方向走，但不要穿过南门，而要在它前面右转。走过第一座塔之后你们就能看到右手边的猎鸟表演。
(Q19) At 3 pm there's a short performance of traditional dancing on the outdoor stage. 下午三点，在露天舞台上有一场短短的传统舞蹈的表演。
That's right at the other side of the castle from the entrance, and over the bridge. 进入正门后过桥，表演就在城堡的另一头。
It's about ten minutes' walk or so. 大概要走十分钟左右。
(Q20) And finally the shop. It's actually inside one of the towers but the way in is from the outside. 最后是商店。实际上它位于一座塔的里面，但你们得从外面进去。
Just take the first left after the main entrance, go down the path and take the first right. It's got some lovely gifts and souvenirs. 在进入正门后的第一个路口左转，沿着小路走，再在第一个路口右转。店里有许多不错的礼物和纪念品。
Right, so we're just arriving... 好的，我们即将到达的是...