(Q11（单选）) Good morning, my name is Erica Matthews and I'm the owner of Matthews Island Holidays, a company set up by my parents. 大家早上好。我叫Erica Matthews，是Matthews Island Holidays旅游公司的负责人。这家公司是由我的父母创办的。
Thank you for coming to this presentation, in which I hope to interest you in what we have to offer. 感谢大家前来参加这场介绍会，希望通过今天的分享，让大家对我们的旅游产品产生兴趣。
[定位词一直只有一个company，注意力要集中； ❌C，否定原文， don't aim to 竞争 on The number of ...] We're a small family-run company, and we believe in the importance of the personal touch, so we don't aim to compete with other companies on the number of customers. 我们是一家小型家族企业，非常重视个性化服务，因此我们并不追求在客户数量上与其他公司竞争。
[✅A， man years ... more than ...; ❌B 否定原文， a small number of 目的地] What we do is build on our many years' experience more than almost any other rail holiday company to ensure we provide perfect holidays and a small number of destinations which we've got to know extremely well. 凭借多年积累的经验，我们比大多数铁路旅游公司更专注于少数几个目的地，并力求为客户打造最优质的旅行体验。
(Q12) [专有名词定位] I'll start with our 6-day Isle of Man holiday. 接下来我先为大家介绍我们的六天马恩岛之旅。
This is a fascinating island in the Irish sea, with Wales to the south, England to the east, Scotland to the north, and Northern Ireland to the west. 马恩岛位于爱尔兰海上，是一个非常迷人的岛屿。它南面是威尔士，东面是英格兰，北面是苏格兰，西面则是北爱尔兰。
[✅B， start 标志可能有【顺序】出现，manager定位词出现—— - then] Our holiday starts in Heysham, where your tour manager will meet you, then you'll travel by ferry to the Isle of Man. 我们的旅程从Heysham开始，届时领队会在那里与大家会合，然后一起乘坐渡轮前往马恩岛。
[❌C/A， 都提到，但偷换概念，题目问的是能见到tour manager的] Some people prefer to fly from Luton instead and another popular option is to go by train to Liverpool and take a ferry from there. 有些游客更喜欢从卢顿乘飞机出发；另一种热门选择则是先乘火车前往利物浦，再从那里搭乘渡轮。
(Q13) [定位词price ➕    covers = included  ➕ lunch定位词 on the 3 days ✅A] You have 5 nights in the hotel and the price covers 5 breakfast and dinners and lunch on the 3 days when there are organized trips. 行程包含五晚酒店住宿，价格还包括五顿早餐、五顿晚餐，以及三天团队活动期间的午餐。
[❌four， five都是干扰项， 4说的是第4天自由活动， 5说的是 一共5晚] Day 4 is free and most people have lunch in a cafe or restaurant in Douglas. 第四天为自由活动时间，大多数游客会选择在Douglas的咖啡馆或餐厅享用午餐。
The price of the holiday includes the ferry to the Isle of Man, all travel on the island, the hotel and the meals I've mentioned. 团费包含往返马恩岛的渡轮费用、岛上所有交通费用、酒店住宿以及刚才提到的餐饮安排。
(Q14) Incidentally, we tried to make booking our holidays as simple and fair as possible. 顺便提一下，我们一直努力让预订流程尽可能简单且公平。
[定位词 画的是 pay extra（含义上表示价格）， 原文出现price。 ❌B，否定] So, unlike with many companies, the price is the same whether you book six months in advance or at the last minute. 因此，与许多旅游公司不同，无论你提前六个月预订还是临近出发时才预订，价格都完全一样。
[supplement 也是表示额外费用，专注等答案句出现。] And there's no supplement for single rooms in hotels. 此外，单人入住酒店也无需支付额外费用。（单词📒：supplement (旅行或住宾馆等所付的) 额外费用）
[✅C， change the start date = transfer to another date， change=transfer] If you make a booking, then need to change the start date, for example because of illness. 如果您已经预订，但后来因为生病等原因需要更改出发日期，
[for ... fee = pay extra] You're welcome to change to an alternative date to a different tour for a small administrative fee. 只需支付少量手续费，就可以改期或改报其他线路。
(Q15（表格填空 table）) Okay, so what does the holiday consist of? 接下来让我为大家介绍具体行程安排。
Well on Day 1, you'll arrive in time for a short introduction by your tour manager, followed by dinner in the hotel. 第一天，大家抵达后将参加领队组织的简短说明会，随后在酒店享用晚餐。