(Q11（单选）) Good morning, everyone, and welcome to Stevenson's, one of the country's major manufacturers of metal goods. 大家早上好，欢迎来到 Stevenson's 公司，它是全国主要的金属制品制造商之一。（manufacturer = 制造商；metal goods = 金属制品）
Thank you for choosing us for your two weeks of work experience. 感谢大家选择来我们公司进行为期两周的工作实践。（work experience = 工作实践/实习体验，不一定是正式实习）
My name is Julia Simmons, and since the beginning of this year I've been the managing director. 我叫 Julia Simmons，自今年年初起一直担任公司的总经理。（managing director ≈ 总经理、执行总裁）
Stevenson's is quite an old company. Stevenson's 是一家历史相当悠久的公司。
Like me, the founder, Ronald Stevenson, went into the steel industry when he left school – that was in 1923. 和我一样，公司创始人 Ronald Stevenson 也是一毕业就进入了钢铁行业，那是在1923年。（go into an industry = 进入某行业）
He set up this company when he finished his apprenticeship, in 1926, although he actually started making plans two years earlier, in 1924. 1926年完成学徒期后，他创办了这家公司，不过实际上早在1924年他就已经开始筹划了。（听力易错：1924开始规划 → 1926正式创立）
He was a very determined young man! 他当时真是一位意志坚定的年轻人！（determined = 有决心的）
(Q12) Stevenson's long-term plan was to manufacture components for the machine tools industry – although in fact that never came about – and for the automotive industry, that is, cars and lorries. Stevenson 原本的长期计划是为机床行业生产零部件，不过这一计划实际上从未实现；同时也计划为汽车行业，也就是轿车和卡车行业生产零部件。（come about = 发生、实现）
However, there was a delay of five years before that happened, 然而，这一计划推迟了五年才开始实施。
because shortly before the company went into production, 因为就在公司投产前不久， 【go into production = 投产；】
Stevenson was given the opportunity to make goods for hospitals and other players in the healthcare industry, so that's what we did for the first five years. Stevenson 获得了为医院及其他医疗行业机构生产产品的机会，所以公司最初五年一直从事这方面的业务。【players in the healthcare industry = 医疗行业相关机构，而非“玩家”】
(Q13) Over the years, we've expanded the premises considerably – we were lucky that the site is big enough, so moving to a new location has never been necessary. 这些年来，我们大幅扩建了厂区。幸运的是，这块场地足够大，因此从未有必要搬迁到新址。（premises = 场地、厂区、办公区；雅思听力高频，不是“前提”）
However, the layout is far from ideal for modern machinery and production methods, so we intend to carry out major refurbishment of this site over the next five years. 不过，目前的布局对于现代化设备和生产方式来说远非理想，因此未来五年内我们计划对整个厂区进行大规模翻新改造。（layout = 布局；refurbishment = 翻新、改造）
(Q14) I'd better give you some idea of what you'll be doing during your two weeks with us, so you know what to expect. 我最好先给大家介绍一下接下来两周你们会做些什么，好让大家心里有数。（know what to expect = 知道会发生什么，有心理准备）
Most mornings you'll have a presentation from one of the managers, to learn about their department, starting this morning with research and development. 大多数上午，你们都会听一位经理做介绍，了解他们所在的部门。从今天上午开始，第一个部门是研发部。（research and development (R&D) = 研发部）
And you'll all spend some time in each department, observing what's going on and talking to people – 你们还会在各个部门待上一段时间，观察工作情况并与员工交流，
as long as you don't stop them from doing their work altogether! 前提是别把他们的工作完全耽误了！（what's going on = 正在发生什么）
In the past, a teacher from your school has come in at the end of each week to find out how the group were getting on, 过去，每周结束时学校都会派一位老师来了解大家的实习情况，
but your school isn't able to arrange that this year. 但今年学校无法做出这样的安排。（get on = 进展如何）
(Q15（地图）) OK, now I'll briefly help you to orientate yourselves around the site. 好的，现在我简单带大家熟悉一下厂区布局。（地图题高频；orientate yourself = 熟悉环境、辨认方位）
As you can see, we're in the reception area, which we try to make attractive and welcoming to visitors. 如大家所见，我们现在所在的是接待区，我们尽量把这里布置得美观且让来访者感到宾至如归。
There's a corridor running left from here, and if you go along that, the door facing you at the end is the entrance to the coffee room. 从这里向左有一条走廊，沿着走廊一直走到底，正对面的那扇门就是咖啡休息室的入口。（地图题高频；facing you = 正对着你）
This looks out onto the main road on one side, and some trees on the other, and that'll be where you meet each morning. 咖啡休息室一侧朝向主干道，另一侧能看到树木，以后大家每天早上就在这里集合。（look out onto = 面向、俯瞰）
(Q16) The factory is the very big room on the far side of the site. 工厂车间位于整个厂区最里面的那间大型建筑内。（far side = 最远的一侧）
Next to it is the warehouse, which can be accessed by lorries going up the road to the turning area at the end. 旁边就是仓库，卡车可以沿道路开到尽头的掉头区后进入仓库。（warehouse = 仓库；turning area = 掉头区）
You can get to the warehouse by crossing to the far side of the courtyard, and then the door is on your right. 穿过庭院到对面后，右手边那扇门就是仓库入口。（courtyard = 庭院）
(Q17) Somewhere you'll be keen to find is the staff canteen. 我想你们最想知道的位置之一就是员工餐厅了。
This is right next to reception. 它就在接待区旁边。
I can confidently say that the food's very good, but the view isn't. 我可以很有信心地说，这里的饭菜很好吃，不过景色就一般了。
The windows on one side look onto a corridor and courtyard, which aren't very attractive at all, and on the other onto the access road, which isn't much better. 一侧窗户对着走廊和庭院，并不怎么好看；另一侧则朝向通行道路，也没好到哪里去。（access road = 连接道路、通道）
(Q18) You'll be using the meeting room quite often, and you'll find it by walking along the corridor to the left of the courtyard, and continuing along it to the end. 你们会经常使用会议室。从庭院左侧的走廊一直往前走到底就能找到它。
The meeting room is the last one on the right, and I'm afraid there's no natural daylight in the room. 会议室是右手边最后一间，不过遗憾的是里面没有自然采光。（natural daylight = 自然光）
(Q19) Then you'll need to know where some of the offices are. 接下来大家还需要了解几个办公室的位置。
The human resources department is at the front of this building, so you head to the left along the corridor from reception, and it's the second room you come to. 人力资源部位于这栋楼的前部。从接待区沿左侧走廊前进，它是你经过的第二个房间。（human resources department = 人力资源部，HR）
It looks out onto the main road. 办公室窗户朝向主路。
(Q20) And finally, the boardroom, where you'll be meeting sometimes. 最后是董事会议室，你们有时也会在那里开会。（boardroom = 董事会议室）
That has quite a pleasant view, as it looks out on to the trees. 那里景色相当不错，因为窗外就是树林。
Go along the corridor past the courtyard, right to the end. 沿着走廊经过庭院，一直走到尽头。
The boardroom is on the left, next to the factory. 董事会议室就在左侧，紧挨着工厂车间。
OK, now are there any questions before we … 好的，在我们继续之前，大家有什么问题吗？