(Q11（单选）) Good morning and thank you for coming here today. 大家早上好，感谢各位今天来到这里。
I'd like to bring you up to date with changes in the school that will affect your children. 我想向大家介绍一下学校近期的一些变化，这些变化会影响到你们的孩子。（bring someone up to date with = 向某人更新最新情况）
As you know, the school buildings date from various times: some from the 1970s, some from the last five years, and of course Dartfield House is over a century old. 正如大家所知道的，学校里的建筑建于不同时期：有些建于20世纪70年代，有些是在过去五年内建成的，当然，达特菲尔德楼已有一百多年历史了。（date from = 追溯至、建于）
It was commissioned by a businessman, Neville Richards, and intended as his family home, but he died before it was completed. 这栋建筑是由商人内维尔·理查兹出资建造的，本来打算作为他的家庭住宅，但他在工程完工前就去世了。（commission ≠ 委托别人做作业，而是“出资建造、委托建设”）
His heir chose to sell it to the local council, who turned it into offices. 他的继承人决定把它卖给当地政府，而政府后来把它改建成了办公场所。（heir = 继承人）
A later plan to convert it into a tourist information centre didn't come about, through lack of money, and instead it formed the nucleus of this school when it opened 40 years ago. 后来曾有计划把它改建成旅游信息中心，但由于资金不足未能实现；相反，40年前学校成立时，它成为了学校最核心的建筑。（come about = 发生、实现；nucleus = 核心、中心）
(Q12) The school has grown as the local population has increased, and I can now give you some news about the lower school site, which is separated from the main site by a road. 随着当地人口增长，学校规模也不断扩大。现在我想告诉大家一些关于低年级校区的消息，这个校区与主校区之间隔着一条马路。（site = 校区、场地）
Planning permission has been granted for development of both sites. 两个校区的开发建设规划许可都已经获批。（英国常考词：planning permission = 建筑规划许可）
The lower school will move to new buildings that will be constructed on the main site. 低年级校区将搬迁到主校区内新建的教学楼中。
Developers will construct houses on the existing lower school site. 开发商将在目前低年级校区的原址上建造住宅。
Work on the new school buildings should start within the next few months. 新教学楼的建设预计将在未来几个月内启动。
(Q13) A more imminent change concerns the catering facilities and the canteen. 一个更迫在眉睫的变化与餐饮设施和食堂有关。（imminent = 即将发生的；catering facilities = 餐饮设施）
The canteen is always very busy throughout the lunch period – in fact it's often full to capacity, because a lot of our pupils like the food that's on offer there. 午餐时间食堂总是非常繁忙。事实上，它经常座无虚席，因为很多学生都喜欢那里提供的食物。【full to capacity = 满员】
But there's only one serving point, so most pupils have to wait a considerable time to be served. 不过，目前只有一个取餐窗口，因此大多数学生都需要等待相当长时间。【serving point = 供餐窗口】
This is obviously unsatisfactory, as they may have hardly finished their lunch before afternoon lessons start. 显然，这种情况并不理想，因为学生们可能还没吃完午饭，下午的课程就开始了。
So we've had a new Food Hall built, and this will come into use next week. 因此我们新建了一座餐饮大厅，下周就将投入使用。（come into use = 开始投入使用）
(Q14) It'll have several serving areas, and I'll give you more details about those in a minute, 新餐饮大厅将设有多个供餐区域，稍后我会详细介绍。
but one thing we ask you to do, to help in the smooth running of the Food Hall, is to discuss with your children each morning which type of food they want to eat that day, 不过，为了保证它顺利运作，我们希望各位家长每天早晨和孩子提前商量好当天想吃什么，【smooth running = 顺利运转】
so they can go straight to the relevant serving point. 这样他们就能直接前往相应的供餐窗口。【relevant = 相应的、对应的】
There won't be any junk food – everything on offer will be healthy – 这里不会提供垃圾食品，所有供应的食物都会是健康食品。
and there's no change to the current system of paying for lunches by topping up your child's electronic payment card online. 另外，目前通过网上充值孩子电子饭卡支付午餐费用的方式也不会改变。（top up = 充值）
(Q15) You may be wondering what will happen to the old canteen. 大家可能想知道旧食堂将会如何处理。
We'll still have tables and chairs in there, and pupils can eat food from the Food Hall or lunch they've brought from home. 里面仍然会保留桌椅，学生们可以在那里吃从新餐饮大厅购买的食物，或者自己从家里带来的午餐。
Eventually we may use part of the canteen for storage, but first we'll see how many pupils go in there at lunchtime. 将来我们可能会把食堂的一部分改作储藏空间，不过首先要观察午餐时间有多少学生会继续使用它。（storage = 储存空间）
(Q16（配对）) OK, back to the serving points in the Food Hall, which will all have side dishes, desserts and drinks on sale, as well as main courses. 好的，回到餐饮大厅的供餐区。除了主菜之外，每个供餐区都会出售配菜、甜点和饮料。（side dishes = 配菜）
One serving point we call World Adventures. 其中一个供餐区名叫“世界美食之旅”。
This will serve a different country's cuisine each day, maybe Chinese one day and Lebanese the next. 这里每天都会提供不同国家的菜肴，比如今天是中国菜，明天可能就是黎巴嫩菜。（cuisine = 某国菜系）
The menus will be planned for a week at a time, so pupils will know what's going to be available the whole of that week. 菜单将按周制定，因此学生们可以提前知道整周会提供哪些食物。
(Q17) Street Life is also international, with food from three particular cultures. “Street Life”也是一个国际化窗口，供应来自三个特定文化地区的街头美食。
We'll ask pupils to make suggestions, so perhaps sometimes there'll be food from Thailand, Ethiopia and Mexico, and then one of them will be replaced by Jamaican food for a week or two. 我们会征求学生们的建议，所以有时可能供应泰国、埃塞俄比亚和墨西哥的食物，然后其中一种会被牙买加美食替换一两周。
(Q18) The Speedy Italian serving point will cater particularly for the many pupils who don't eat meat or fish: they can be sure that all the food served there is suitable for them. “Speedy Italian”窗口主要面向不吃肉或鱼的学生，他们可以放心，因为那里供应的所有食物都适合他们食用。⚠️ 易错点：这里很多同学会听成 Italian food = 意大利菜，但题目真正考的是 don't eat meat or fish → vegetarian（素食者），所以重点不是“意大利菜”，而是“适合素食学生”。
There'll be plenty of variety, so they shouldn't get bored with the food. 那里会提供丰富多样的选择，因此学生们不太会吃腻。
(Q19&20（多选）) OK, that's all on the new Food Hall. 好的，关于新餐饮大厅的介绍就到这里。
Now after-school lessons. 接下来谈谈课后课程。
These are very popular with pupils, particularly swimming – in fact there's a waiting list for lessons. 这些课程非常受学生欢迎，尤其是游泳课，事实上现在已经有候补名单了。（waiting list = 等候名单）
Cycling is another favourite, and I'm delighted that dozens of pupils make use of the chance to learn to ride in off-road conditions. 骑自行车课程也很受欢迎，我很高兴看到几十名学生利用这个机会学习在非铺装路面环境下骑行。（off-road = 越野环境）
It means that more and more cycle to and from school every day. 这意味着越来越多的学生每天骑车上下学。
As you know, we have a well-equipped performance centre, and we're going to start drama classes in there, too. 正如大家所知，我们拥有设施完善的表演中心，而我们也将在那里开设戏剧课程。
Pupils will be able to join in just for fun or work up to taking part in a play – we hope to put on at least one a year. 学生既可以把它当作兴趣活动参加，也可以逐步提升到参演正式戏剧。我们希望每年至少上演一部戏剧作品。（work up to = 逐步达到；put on a play = 上演戏剧）
We already teach a number of pupils to use the sound and lighting systems in the centre. 我们已经在教授部分学生如何操作表演中心的音响和灯光系统。
And a former pupil has given a magnificent grand piano to the school, so a few pupils will be able to learn at the school instead of going to the local college, as many of them do at the moment. 另外，一位校友向学校捐赠了一架非常出色的大三角钢琴，因此今后部分学生可以直接在学校学习钢琴，而不必像目前许多人那样前往当地学院学习。（former pupil = 校友；grand piano = 三角钢琴，IELTS高频听力词）