(Q11&12（多选）) Good afternoon. My name's Mrs Carter and I run the before and after school extended hours childcare service. 下午好。我叫 Carter 女士，负责学校的课前和课后延时托管服务。run（负责、管理）；extended hours childcare service（延时托管服务）
I hope you've had a chance to have a good look around the school and talk to staff and pupils. 希望大家已经有机会好好参观学校，并和老师及学生交流过。have a chance to；have a good look around（好好参观）
I know that many of you are interested in using our childcare service when your child joins the school, and perhaps you already know something about it, but for those that don't, I'll go through the main details now. 我知道很多家长都打算在孩子入学后使用我们的托管服务，也许有些人已经有所了解，不过对于还不了解的家长，我现在会介绍一下主要情况。be interested in；join the school（入学）；go through（逐一介绍）
[D❌] We offer childcare for children from the ages of four to eleven both before and after school. 我们为4岁到11岁的儿童提供课前和课后的托管服务。offer childcare（提供托管服务）
I know that many parents who work find this service invaluable. 我知道很多上班的家长都觉得这项服务非常宝贵。invaluable（极其有价值的）
You can leave your child with us safe in the knowledge that they will be extremely well cared for. 您可以放心把孩子交给我们，因为他们会得到非常周到的照顾。safe in the knowledge that…（放心，因为……）；be well cared for（得到妥善照顾）
[E✅] We are insured to provide care for up to 70 children, although we rarely have this many attending at any one session. 我们的保险允许我们最多照看70名儿童，不过每场托管几乎不会有这么多人。be insured to do；up to；at any one session
[B✅，C❌] I think we generally expect around 50–60 children for the afternoon sessions and about half that number for the breakfast sessions. 通常下午托管会有大约50到60名孩子，而早餐托管的人数大约只有一半。expect around；breakfast session
Although we currently do have 70 children registered with us, not all of these attend every day. 虽然目前有70名孩子在我们这里注册，但并不是每个人每天都会来。be registered with（注册在……）
[A❌] It's ten years since we began offering an extended hours service and we've come a long way during that time. 我们开展延时托管服务已经有十年了，这期间取得了很大的发展。It's…since…；come a long way（取得巨大进步）
When we first opened, we only had about 20 children attending regularly. 刚开始运营时，只有大约20名孩子会定期参加。attend regularly
(Q13（单选）) We try to keep our costs as low as we can and we think we provide very good value for money. 我们尽量把收费保持在最低水平，同时也相信我们的服务物有所值。keep costs low；value for money（物超所值）
[Q13答案句] For the afternoon sessions, which run from 3.30 until 6 p.m., it's £7.20. 下午托管从3点半持续到6点，费用是7.2英镑。run from…until…
But if you prefer, you can pay for one hour only, which costs £3.50, or two hours which costs £5.70. 当然，如果您愿意，也可以按小时付费，一小时3.5英镑，两小时5.7英镑。pay for；if you prefer
(Q14) The cost of the childcare includes food and snacks. 托管费用已经包含正餐和零食。include
They'll be given breakfast in the morning and in the afternoon, a healthy snack as soon as they finish school. 孩子们早上会吃早餐，下午一放学就会提供健康的小吃。healthy snack；as soon as
[Q14答案句C] At 5 p.m. children are given something more substantial, such as pasta or a casserole. 下午5点，孩子们会吃一顿更正式、更有饱腹感的食物，比如意大利面或炖菜。substantial meal（更有分量的一餐）；casserole（炖菜）
[❌A， 否定] Please inform us of any allergies that your child might have and we'll make sure they're offered a suitable alternative. 如果您的孩子有任何过敏情况，请提前告诉我们，我们会提供合适的替代餐食。inform sb of；allergy；a suitable alternative
(Q15) As you may know, the childcare service runs through the school holidays from 8 a.m. to 6 p.m. 大家可能知道，我们的托管服务在学校假期期间也照常开放，时间是早上8点到下午6点。run through the school holidays
We offer a really varied and exciting programme to keep the children entertained – we don't want them to feel as if they are still at school! 我们安排了丰富又有趣的活动，让孩子们保持开心，我们可不希望他们觉得自己还在上课！varied programme；keep sb entertained（让某人玩得开心）
[Q15答案句 A] It will also feel different because they'll get the chance to make new friends with children from other schools – spaces are available for them 假期托管还有一个不同之处，就是孩子们有机会认识其他学校的新朋友，
[Q15❌C] because a lot of our term-time children don't always attend during the holiday. 因为我们很多平时上学期间参加托管的孩子，假期不一定会来，所以会空出不少名额。【get the chance to；term-time（学期期间）；spaces are available】
[❌Q15 B] In the past, parents have asked if children over the age of 11 are allowed to come with their younger brothers and sisters – but I'm afraid we're unable to do this because of the type of insurance we have. 以前有家长问过，11岁以上的孩子是否可以陪弟弟妹妹一起来，不过由于保险规定，我们无法这样安排。be allowed to；I'm afraid…
(Q16（配对）) So now let me tell you about some of the activities that your child can do during the afterschool sessions. 接下来，我给大家介绍一下孩子们课后托管时可以参加的一些活动。afterschool sessions
As well as being able to use the playground equipment, computers and the library, there is usually at least one 'special' activity that children can do each day. 除了可以使用游乐设施、电脑和图书馆外，每天通常还会安排至少一项特色活动。as well as；playground equipment
For example, Spanish. 例如，西班牙语课程。
We have a specialist teacher coming in every Thursday to give a basic introduction to the language through games and songs. 每周四都会有一位专业老师来，通过游戏和歌曲带孩子们学习西班牙语基础。specialist teacher；a basic introduction to
She does two sessions: one for the over 8s and one for the younger children. 她每次会上两节课，一节给8岁以上的孩子，一节给年龄更小的孩子。the over 8s
This is the only activity which we have to make an extra charge for – but it's well worth it. 这是唯一需要额外收费的活动，不过绝对物有所值。make an extra charge for；be well worth it
(Q17 Music) Once a week the children have the opportunity to do some music. 孩子们每周还有一次参加音乐活动的机会。have the opportunity to
We're very lucky that one of our staff is a member of a folk band. 我们很幸运，一位员工还是一支民谣乐队的成员。folk band
On Mondays, she teaches singing and percussion to groups of children. 每周一，她会教孩子们唱歌和打击乐。percussion（打击乐）
We do rely on parental support for this, so if any of you sing or play an instrument and would be prepared to help out at these sessions, we'd be delighted. 这项活动确实需要家长们的支持，所以如果各位会唱歌或会演奏乐器，并愿意来帮忙，我们会非常欢迎。rely on；help out（帮忙）
(Q18 Painting) Painting continues to be one of the most popular activities. 绘画一直都是最受欢迎的活动之一。continue to be
To begin with we weren't keen on offering this because of the extra mess involved, but children kept asking if they could do some art and so we finally gave in. 一开始我们并不想开设绘画活动，因为收拾起来特别麻烦，但孩子们一直要求参加，所以最后我们还是妥协了。be keen on；mess involved；give in（让步）
Art is great for helping the children to relax after working hard at school all day. 绘画非常有助于孩子们在学校学习了一整天之后放松下来。be great for；relax after…
(Q19 Yoga) Yoga is something that we've been meaning to introduce for some time but haven't been able to find anyone available to teach it – until now that is. 瑜伽是我们一直想引入的课程，只是之前一直找不到合适的老师，不过现在终于找到了。have been meaning to do（一直想做）；until now
So we'll see how this goes. 所以我们会看看效果如何。see how it goes（看看进展如何，口语高频）
Hopefully, children will benefit in all sorts of ways from this. 希望孩子们能从中在各个方面受益。benefit from；in all sorts of ways
(Q20 Cooking) Cooking is another popular activity. 烹饪也是另一项很受欢迎的活动。
They make a different sort of cake, or pizza or bread each week. 每周他们都会制作不同种类的蛋糕、披萨或面包。a different sort of
Although the younger children love doing it, we found that the mess was just too much, so we've decided to restrict this to the over 8s, as they are better able to clean up after themselves. 虽然年龄小的孩子也很喜欢烹饪，但我们发现现场实在太乱了，因此决定把这项活动限制在8岁以上的孩子参加，因为他们更能够自己收拾整理。restrict…to…（限制……）；clean up after themselves（自己收拾干净）